[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the sitcom Cheers what was the name of the restaurant that sat above the bar?", "correct_answer": "Melvilles", "incorrect_answers": ["Melvins", "Mickeys", "Minnies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the two largest veins in the body?", "correct_answer": "Vena cavae", "incorrect_answers": ["Pulmonary veins", "Coronary veins", "Atria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a pen, what is the object that holds the ink called?", "correct_answer": "ink reservoir", "incorrect_answers": ["ink composite", "ink compress", "ink tube"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This British philologist and student of ancient India is famous for his theory of the existence of a relationship among Indo-European languages.", "correct_answer": "Sir William Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Sir Mark Waverley Park", "Sir Malcom Edwards", "Jonathan Parker-Knolls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After Hurricane Katrina, evacuees from Louisiana, Mississippi, and Alabama were granted two months of food stamps and free gasoline from the Texas Department of Health and Human Services.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character does Tom Cruise portray in the 1993 thriller movie The Firm?", "correct_answer": "Attorney", "incorrect_answers": ["Businessman", "FBI agent", "Assassin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which transit of planets against the Sun obscures the most of its disk?", "correct_answer": "Transit of Jupiter, viewed from Saturn", "incorrect_answers": ["Transit of Earth, viewed from Mars", "Transit of Uranus, viewed from Neptune", "Transit of Saturn, viewed from Uranus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This species, considered to have colonized almost every landmass on Earth, is studied by myrmecology.", "correct_answer": "ants", "incorrect_answers": ["bees", "flies", "hornets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This observatory, located at Mauna Kea, Hawaii, uses two telescopes equipped with adaptive optics.", "correct_answer": "W. M. Keck Observatory", "incorrect_answers": ["Paranal Observatory", "Observatorio Nacional de Llano del Hato", "Roque de los Muchachos Observatory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Galaxy that our Solar System is a part of?", "correct_answer": "Milky Way", "incorrect_answers": ["The Large Magellanic Cloud", "Andromeda", "Hollywood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what southern state is the movie Steel Magnolias set?", "correct_answer": "Louisiana", "incorrect_answers": ["Alabama", "Georgia", "Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements is true about snails?", "correct_answer": "Snails do have tooth-like formations.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Snails do not have any teeth or tooth-like formations.", "Snails have real teeth very similar to those of mammals."]}]